ecartservice.net 2016-05-12

# Privacy | eCartService.net

## Privacy & Disclosure

We respect your right to privacy. None of the personally identifying information we collect is passed on for use by other parties without your consent, unless as required under UK law.

## Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text information created by websites and stored on your computer. Our software may use cookies to help maintain certain visit related data while browsing our site.

### Non-personally Identifying Information

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, please refer to the [Google Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Specifically:

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

## Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can browse our Site without disclosing your personal data.

## Consent

Your submission of any personally identifying information to this site is deemed to be your consent for us to store the information you provide.

## Links to other Websites

Parts of our Site contain links to third party websites for your convenience and information. If you use these links, you will leave the site. When you access a third party site, please understand that we do not control the content and are not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. We suggest that you carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those third party website linked to our site. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If there are changes or additions to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our Site so that you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have. Please be sure to check our Privacy Policy before proceeding to use our Site. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will always use your personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you give your express consent for us to do otherwise.
